https://www.forexsignal.com/privacy-policy.html

Forex SignalsHow it worksPricing and PlansFAQBlogTRADE RESULTSTrade CopierTrend TraderMentoringBrokerContact UsPRICING & SIGNUP Forex Signals | Forex Trading Signal | FX Trade Signals > Privacy Policy
Security and DisclosureForexSignal.com (“4XFindMe”) respects each individual’s right to privacy. We value our relationship with you, and we take pride in maintaining loyalty and respect with each individual client by providing you with security. The provisions of this notice apply to former clients as well as our current clients.Personal InformationWhen you apply for or maintain a live account with ForexSignal.com, we collect personal information about you for business purposes, such as evaluating your financial needs, processing your requests and transactions, informing you about products and services that may be of interest to you, and providing customer service. Such information may include:NameEmail AddressPhone NumberPhysical AddressTrading/Risk CapitalThe broker you are usingAbout CookiesCookies are small files containing information that a Web site uses to track its visitors. ForexSignal.com may set and access ForexSignal.com cookies on your computer, enabling us to learn which advertisements and promotions bring users to our Web site. ForexSignal.com or any of its divisions may use cookies in connection with ForexSignal.com’s products and services to track your activities on our Web sites. Such information that we collect and share would be anonymous and not personally identifiable.Security TechnologyForexSignal.com uses Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology in order to protect certain information that you submit. This type of technology protects you from having your information intercepted by anyone other than ForexSignal.com while it is being transmitted to us. We work hard to ensure that our Web sites are secure and that they meet industry standards. We also use other safeguards such as firewalls, authentication systems (e.g., passwords and personal identification numbers), and access control mechanisms to control unauthorized access to systems and data. Sharing Information WithThird PartiesForexSignal.com does not disclose your personal information to third parties, except as described in this Policy. Third party disclosures may include sharing such information with non-affiliated companies that perform support services for your account or facilitate your transactions with ForexSignal.com, including those that provide professional, legal, or accounting advice to ForexSignal.com. Non-affiliated companies that assist ForexSignal.com in providing services to you are required to maintain the confidentiality of such information to the extent they receive it and to use your personal information only in the course of providing such services and only for the purposes that ForexSignal.com dictates.We may also disclose your personal information to third parties to fulfill your instructions or pursuant to your expressed consent.We want you to know that ForexSignal.com will not sell your personal information.Regulatory DisclosureUnder limited circumstances, ForexSignal.com may disclose your personal information to third parties as permitted by, or to comply with, applicable laws and regulations. For example, we may disclose personal information to cooperate with regulatory authorities and law enforcement agencies to comply with subpoenas or other official requests, and as necessary to protect our rights or property. Except as described in this privacy policy, we will not use your personal information for any other purpose, unless we describe how such information will be used at the time you disclose it to us or we obtain your permission.Opt OutYou are not required to supply any of the personal information that we may request; however, failure to do so may result in our being unable to open or maintain your account or to provide services to you. While we make every effort to ensure that all information we hold about you is accurate, complete, and up to date, you can help us considerably in this regard by promptly notifying us if there are any changes to your personal information.If you do not wish to have your personal information disclosed to our affiliates or other third parties as described in this Policy, please contact us via e-mail at: info@forexsignal.comor send your request to:ForexSignal.comAttention: Privacy Officer33332 Valle Road, Suite 250San Juan Capistrano, CA 92675United States
7 Day Trial OfferGet OfferNewsletter
@forexsignalcom Follow
InstagramLoad More...Follow on Instagram ForexSignal BlogTry it TodayNo time to trade?Facebook Trading the Forex Market With Transparency Since 1998.Real-Time Forex trade signal alerts on any mobile phone in 200+ countries.Powerful cloud based forex signal software compatible with Desktop and Mobile devices.Follow our Forex signals on your own or have our signals auto traded directly to your account.Affiliate ProgramFAQPrivacy PolicyTerms & ConditionsRisk Warning Legally required risk warning - Trading foreign exchange on margin carries a high level of risk, and may not be suitable for all investors. The high degree of leverage can work against you as well as for you. Before deciding to invest in foreign exchange you should carefully consider your investment objectives, level of experience, and risk appetite. The possibility exists that you could sustain a loss of some or all of your initial investment and therefore you should not invest money that you cannot afford to lose. You should be aware of all the risks associated with foreign exchange trading, and seek advice from an independent financial advisor if you have any doubts.
Hypothetical performance results have many inherent limitations. No representation is being made that any account will or is likely
to achieve profits or losses similar to those shown. In fact, there are frequently sharp differences between hypothetical performance
results and the actual results subsequently achieved by any particularly trading program. One of the limitations of hypothetical
performance results is that they are generally prepared with the benefit of hindsight. In addition, hypothetical trading does not
involve financial risk. Variables such as the ability to adhere to a particular trading program in spite of trading losses as well as
maintaining adequate liquidity are material points which can adversely affect actual real trading results. Currency trading involves
high risk and you can lose a lot of money.All Trade Copier Signals generated to the client account are manageable and can be overridden by the subscriber in the client account. The subscriber reserves the right and ability to reject, close, terminate or disable the Trade Copier signals at any time.Terms and Conditions: Subscribing to our service means you agree with our terms and conditions. Click here to view.
